shinjiru.com 2006-12-31

# Malaysia & Offshore Web Hosting - Privacy Shinjiru.COM

Shinjiru.COM recognises the importance of your privacy in participation of any kinds of online interaction. Shinjiru.COM is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users.

The following statements outline our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering our webpages to you, Shinjiru.COM does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address without your voluntary participation (see next section).

However, Shinjiru.COM does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example).

In addition, Shinjiru.COM is required to log the IP address of accessing computers address for the purpose of auditing by our advertisers and for our own protection against malicious attacks. (Such as banning a known hacker's or spammer's IP address.) 

The information collected by Shinjiru.COM is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

**Voluntary Participation**

In some cases where you choose to make your own information available to other visitors, you do so at your own risk and Shinjiru.COM believes that it is beyond reasonable doubt that you are aware of such risk. Such cases include, but are not limited to your participation as a user of the classified ads, forums or hyper-linked website on this website.

At our advertisers request, you may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information to participate in the advertisers' promotions or surveys etc. Shinjiru.COM may collect on behalf of the advertisers your personal information. If this does occur, Shinjiru.COM will make reasonable attempts to highlight this to you, by way of a clause in the instructions, beside the "submit" button or similarly prominent areas regarded as noticable by Shinjiru.COM. Should you dispute our judgement of noticability, please do not participate in the promotion or survey etc. You can email to us for an inquiry.

In all other cases which you voluntarily reveal your personal information, such as but not limited to email correspondences, requests, questions, feedback, suggestions etc, we will not divulge your personal particulars without your consent.

**Data Collection**

Shinjiru.COM, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. (Example: To remember that you have voted on our ballot box.) Shinjiru.COM cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. 

For example, our "ballot cookie" is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Shinjiru.COM receives your vote on the ballot. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Shinjiru.COM ensure that we don't ask you to vote on the same motion multiple times.

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

* * *

If you have any additional questions about Shinjiru.COM's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [webmaster@shinjiru.com.my](mailto:webmaster@shinjiru.com.my)
